

ABOUT ME

Finance

A Finance Professional currently learning Data Science and it's applications in finance. CFA Level 3 Candidate. Past experience in digital marketing and managing small portfolios. Interested in Asset Management and Equity Research. See the articles I've written on Medium.

EXPERIENCE

The Starter Labs

Jan 2019 - March 2019 | Digital Marketing Executive

The Starter Labs is a startup focused on providing digital marketing services to Mumbai based clients. Created content, wrote copy, managed Facebook ads and Facebook pixels, and handled Instagram accounts of various brands

CATKING Educare

October 2018 – December 2018 | Business development associate

Business development and sales

EDUCATION

Usha Pravin Gandhi College of Management 2015 – 2018 | Bachelor of Management Studies

Lilavatibai Podar Senior Secondary School 2011 – 2015 | ISC, Science

PROJECTS

A complete data science guided project for the IBM Data science specialization

CERTIFICATIONS

CFA Level 2 ≥

2021 November

CFA Institute Investment Foundations Program ≥ 2022 March

Financial Markets by Yale University

∠
2022 May

Google Data Analytics Professional Certificate

∠
2022 March

SKILLS

Python

Beginner

Only data science applications in jupyter notebooks

Jupyter notebooks Git Github Dash

Other

Other skills

CONTACT

parvaizwork@gmail.com / parvaizmansoori.github.io / +91 8779632556 /

Tap here to download as PDF ∠